export const data=[
    {
        question:"Javascript is an _____ language?",
        option1:"Object Oriented",
        option2:"Object_based",
        option3:"Procedural",
        option4:"None of the above",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following keyword is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        option1:"var",
        option2:"let",
        option3:"Both A and B",
        option4:"None of the above",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
        option1:"getElementbyId()",
        option2:"getElementsByClassName()",
        option3:"Both A and B",
        option4:"None of the above",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Upon encountering empty statements,what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
        option1:"Throws an error",
        option2:"Ignores the statements",
        option3:"Gives a warning",
        option4:"None of the above",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using javascript?",
        option1:"document.write()",
        option2:"console.log()",
        option3:"window.alert()",
        option4:"All of the above",
        ans:4,
    }, {
        question:"How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        option1:"const",
        option2:"var",
        option3:"let",
        option4:"constant",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the use of the <noscript> tag in Javascript?",
        option1:"The contents are displayed by non-JS based browers",
        option2:"Clears all the cookies and cache",
        option3:"both A and B",
        option4:"None of the above",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"When an operator's value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
        option1:"Boolean",
        option2:"Undefined",
        option3:"Object",
        option4:"Integer",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"What does the Javascript 'debugger' statement do?",
        option1:"It will debug all the errors in the program at runtime",
        option2:"It acts as a breakpoint in a program",
        option3:"It will debug error in the current statement if any",
        option4:"All of the above",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which function is used to serialize an object in to a JSON string in Javascripy?",
        option1:"stringify()",
        option2:"parse()",
        option3:"convert()",
        option4:"None of the above",
        ans:1,
    }
]